<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Chris Oswald</title>
    <link>http://chso.me/post/index.xml</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Chris Oswald</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 22:23:00 -0800</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://chso.me/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>About me.</title>
      <link>http://chso.me/post/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 22:23:00 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://chso.me/post/about/</guid>
      <description>

&lt;h2 id=&#34;my-name-is-chris-oswald&#34;&gt;My name is Chris Oswald&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been interested in information security for a long time now, and only now have I really been focusing on my aspirations to join the field. When I was younger, I decided to install Linux, although shortly after I was always falling back to Windows. During these brief periods, I&amp;rsquo;d always learn as much as I could about the linux ecosystem and the tools it provided. One of these tools, was GPG, allowing you to encrypt and sign sets of data and communication, most commonly used in emails. This small find ignited a spark for me in infosec; that entire summer I focused on cryptography and secure methods of communication which brought me around to XMPP and various other protocols for securing data and authentication.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;With this knowledge I really&amp;hellip; didn&amp;rsquo;t do anything with it. I was falling behind in public school, just because I couldn&amp;rsquo;t get my act together and finish assignments and readings, but instead I was either playing games or lying to myself. The next year I finished off with something around a 3.3 or 3.4 GPA, the first time I had ever gotten anything above &lt;strong&gt;2.x&lt;/strong&gt;. Shortly after I started running Linux full time (I now run OpenSUSE tumbleweed) and focusing on my passion in security.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>